

# THERESA NEATE

DEVOPS / QA /
DEVELOPER RELATIONS /
LEADERSHIP

# **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Theresa Neate is a QA practice lead & developer advocate - with several years of leadership experience - who loves lean and agility and advocates for holistic system quality and systems thinking.

Please note: NOT a "DevOps Engineer".

# **ROLE PREFERENCE**

- platforms & cloud platform & platform thinking
- ideally, including AWS (or GCP)
- systems & operations
- Head Of, Exec Mgr, VP ... (or their deputy)
- keep my tech skills sharp/sharper
- degree of operations/ networking/ Python/ AWS/ flavours work
- more technology, not less
- support to complete Diploma of Networking (& who knows what next)
- balance of strategy / hands-on / management (will always bring Lead QA thinking to the table too)

# COMPETENCIES

- Leadership
- Technical literacy and strong interest
- A range of technical skills, most at the level of "serious playing" and some at "full time specialist" level (including a range of AWS services, Java, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, Buildkite, Docker, Linux, Selenium, SQL, etc.)
- System thinking
- Strong communication skills
- Public Speaking
- Coaching & Mentoring
- Quality Analysis & Testing

### **CONTACT DETAILS**

Email: theresanmail@icloud.com
 Website: https://theresaneate.com
 Github: https://github.com/theresaneate
 LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/neatet/
 Twitter: https://twitter.com/TheresaNeate

Location: Melbourne Australia

# **CAREER HISTORY**

#### **Lead Quality Analyst / QA Practice Lead**

REA Group | June 2019 - present

#### **Senior Developer Advocate**

REA Group | June 2018 - June 2019

#### **Lead Quality Analyst / QA Practice Lead**

REA Group | Feb 2016 - June 2018

#### Lead Agile QA

Australia Post | Jan 2013 - Jan 2016

#### **Lead Quality Analyst**

REA Group | Aug 2012 - Dec 2012

#### **Senior QA Consultant**

ThoughtWorks | Aug 2009 - Aug 2012

# Senior Tester, Helpdesk, Executive Manager, Team Lead

Various | pre-2000 - 2009

# TRAINING & EDUCATION

#### (Diploma of Networking

Swinburne University of Technology (Dec 2019)

#### **Graduate Certificate: Business IT**

RMIT University (2016)

#### (withdrawn) Bachelors of IT & Systems

Monash University (2014)

#### **Diploma of IT (General)**

Victoria University (2010)

#### Diploma of IT (Web)

Victoria University (2010)

# **Diploma of Computer Science**

South Africa (pre-2000)

#### **Several short courses & certifications**

Including ISTQB, ISEB, PACT, CCNA2, Ethical Hacking (Web Security), etc.